Do you see that hundreds of agents raided an apartment complex in Chicago in the middle of the night taking children out naked and detaining black U.S. citizens?
This happened around 1 a.m. at a large apartment complex in the South Shore neighborhood of Chicago.
Over 300 agents from ICE, FBI, ATF, and other agents showed up to the apartment complex.
They came with helicopters, some people saying they saw Black Hawk helicopters, and it seems that they also came hidden in budget and U-Haul trucks.
Officials from the government said that they did this because they were looking for six high-priority targets, including suspected members of Tenderagua.
Even though they never showed a warrant while they were there, and they have not confirmed if they actually detained anyone that is a member of Tenderagua.
Agents went into nearly all of the 100 apartments that were in the complex.
They were busting down doors and dragging people out of their beds.
There are reports of kids being zip-tied and being taken out buck naked.
Black residents, who are U.S. citizens, also said that they were dragged out of their apartments.
They were held at gunpoint, asked to give their name, date of birth, and asked if they had any warrant.
They also separated people, Black people in one van and immigrants in the other van.
Reports say that between 30 to 40 people were disappeared that night.
Activists are trying to figure out who were the people that were disappeared since the government is not giving any information on the individuals.
This raid should be a reminder that they're coming for all of us.
Look, white supremacists have done a great job of separating the Black and Latino communities, especially during the last election.
They separated us so then they can come and hunt us down.
They don't care about any of us because of the color of our skin.
And to any white people seeing this and say, not my problem.
Remember, Donald Trump just said that U.S. cities should be training grounds for the military.
And they're starting, as always, with Black and brown bodies.
They're moving to everyone next, white people included.
I'm sorry this is happening to our communities, but we need to stick together.
Like I've always said, we are stronger together.
This is still very much a developing story, so I'll continue bringing information as it comes in.